<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Shop &#8211; Website</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/shop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:32:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>SOTENAS</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/sotenas/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/sotenas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A youthful and festive armchair. This the description of PUCK when it was launched in the 1969 catalogue. We’ve named it SOTENÄS in the Nytillverkad collection, but the design is still by Gillis Lundgren.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A youthful and festive armchair. This the description of PUCK when it was launched in the 1969 catalogue. We’ve named it SOTENÄS in the Nytillverkad collection, but the design is still by Gillis Lundgren.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/sotenas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>POANG X</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/poang-x/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/poang-x/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=207</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[POÄNG armchair has stylish curved lines in bentwood, providing nice support for the neck and comfy resilience. It’s been in our range for several decades and is still just as popular. Want to try it too?]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>POÄNG armchair has stylish curved lines in bentwood, providing nice support for the neck and comfy resilience. It’s been in our range for several decades and is still just as popular. Want to try it too?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/poang-x/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>POANG</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/poang/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/poang/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[POÄNG armchair has stylish curved lines in bentwood, providing nice support for the neck and comfy resilience. It’s been in our range for several decades and is still just as popular. Want to try it too?]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The layer-glued bent wood frame gives the armchair a comfortable resilience, making it perfect to relax in.<br />The high back provides good support for your neck.<br />A variety of seat cushion designs makes it easy to change the look of your POÄNG chair and your living room.<br />To sit even more comfortably and relaxed, you can use the armchair together with a POÄNG ottoman.<br />10-year limited warranty. Read about the terms in the limited warranty brochure.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>Noboru Nakamura</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/poang/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HYLTRAP</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/hyltrap/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/hyltrap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[HYLTARP is an inviting family sofa where everyone wants to spend lots of time. It’s very comfy, has all the essential features – and a classic, clean-lined look that is also pleasing on the eye.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Skillful craftsmanship and a perfect fit means that the sofa will always shows off its best side.<br />The sofa have a soft comfort with high-resilience foam and pocket springs that follow your body and provide support – whether you are sitting, lying down or hanging out on the sofa.<br />Reversible back cushions provide soft support for your back and two different sides to wear. Thanks to the combination of polyester fibers and foam the cushions will retain their shape and comfort year after year.<br />This cover is made of Gransel, a fabric with elements of linen and viscose that add a slight luster. The threads in different sizes create a natural, vibrant expression.<br />The cover is easy to keep clean since it is removable and can be machine washed.<br />A range of coordinated covers makes it easy for you to give your furniture a new look.<br />10 year Limited warranty. Read about the terms in the warranty brochure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/hyltrap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FRIHETEN</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/friheten/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/friheten/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After a good night’s sleep, you can effortlessly convert your bedroom or guest room into a living room again. The built-in storage is easy to access and spacious enough to store bedding, books and PJs.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This sofa converts quickly and easily into a spacious bed when you remove the back cushions and pull out the underframe.<br />Sofa, chaise and double bed in one.<br />Storage space under the chaise. The lid stays open so you can safely and easily take things in and out.<br />You can place the chaise section to the left or right of the sofa, and switch whenever you like.<br />10 year Limited warranty. Read about the terms in the warranty brochure.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>IKEA of Sweden</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/friheten/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>KIVIK</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/kivik/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/kivik/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cuddle up in the comfortable KIVIK sofa. The generous size, low armrests and pocket springs with foam that adapts to the body invites you and your guests to many hours of socializing and relaxation.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enjoy the super comfy KIVIK sofa with deep seat cushions made of pocket springs, high resilience foam and polyester fibers – adding both firm support and relaxing softness.<br />The size and depth of the sofa make it perfect for a nice nap or when the whole family is gathered. There is room for everyone and even extra seating on the wide armrests.<br />The wide armrests have room for everything from your mobile phone to a bowl of movie snacks and very comfortable to lay your head on when you lie down on the sofa for a rest.<br />KIVIK sofa has a strong personality and a clear design language, while the options mean that you can easily match it with your home decor.<br />You can place the chaise section to the left or right of the sofa, and switch whenever you like.<br />The chaise can stand alone or be added onto the sofas.<br />It is easy to combine the sofa with one or more chaise lounges thanks to the removable armrests.<br />Pocket springs are a durable solution that makes the sofa retain both its shape and comfort for many years.<br />The Tresund fabric with a clear texture is made of 100 percent recycled polyester and cotton. It has a nice two-tone effect with a luster and a wonderfully soft feeling that adds to the comfort.<br />The cover is easy to keep clean since it can be machine washed and is easy to take off and put on again.<br />10-year guarantee. Read about the terms in the guarantee brochure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/kivik/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UPPLAND</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/uppland/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/uppland/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=196</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You know the feeling when you sit, lie down or hang out in a sofa, rather than on it. That’s how embracing the deep and generous UPPLAND sofa is – your new favorite place for cozy evenings and lazy days!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enjoy the super comfy UPPLAND sofa with embracing feel and deep seat cushions made of pocket springs, high resilience foam and polyester fibers, adding both firm support and relaxing softness.<br />Reversible back cushions provide soft support for your back and two different sides to wear. Thanks to the combination of polyester fibers and cut foam the cushions will retain their shape and comfort year after year.<br />The cover is easy to keep clean since it is removable and can be machine washed.<br />A range of coordinated covers makes it easy for you to give your furniture a new look.<br />10-year limited warranty. Read about the terms in the limited warranty brochure.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>IKEA of Sweden</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/uppland/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MORABO</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/morabo/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/morabo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Luxury made our way. This sofa has thick grain leather on the exposed surfaces and treated fabric elsewhere – and comes with practical hidden functions like a sofa-bed and storage space under the seat.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The contact surfaces are covered with GRANN – a soft, smooth and strong grain leather with natural variations. Other surfaces have BOMSTAD, a coated fabric that has a similar look and feel to leather.<br />These wooden legs give MORABO sofa and armchair a warm and natural look.<br />The sofa offers you a firm and upright sitting comfort, while your sleeping comfort is enhanced by wooden slats in the construction.<br />You can easily transform the sofa into a bed for 2 – and store the bedlinens in the storage space under the seat to have them close at hand and keep the room tidy when not in use.<br />10-year guarantee. Read about the terms in the guarantee brochure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/morabo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LINANAS</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/linanas/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/linanas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<span style=", system-ui, sans-serif;font-size: 20px">With its soft shapes, modern expressions and durable dark cover, this sofa with a chaise is a perfect combination of function and comfort. Also comes without a chaise if you have less space</span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This cover is made from Vissle fabric in polyester, which is dope-dyed. It’s a durable material with a smooth weave and a nice two-tone effect.<br />The chaise longue can be placed either to the left or right, so you can adapt the sofa to your space and your preferences.<br />10 year Limited warranty. Read about the terms in the warranty brochure.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/linanas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EarBud 1</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/earbud-1/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/earbud-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=63</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/earbud-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
