<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BEDS &#8211; Website</title>
	<atom:link href="/index.php/product-category/bed/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>GLADSTAD</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/gladstad/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/gladstad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The GLADSTAD upholstered bed frame has a clean and modern design, while being comfortable and inviting with its padded headboard and soft cover with a slight texture. Sleep tight – in style!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The GLADSTAD upholstered bed frame is a modern classic with a clean and sleek design.<br />The padded headboard serves as a comfortable backrest, for example when reading or enjoying your weekend breakfast in bed.<br />The soft KABUSA cover has a slight texture and is woven with threads in 3 different grey tones that hide light stains.<br />The simple and versatile design coordinates well with other bedroom furniture and fits perfectly in any modern bedroom.<br />You can easily vacuum under the bed frame to keep the space clean and dust-free.<br />There’s plenty of space under the bed for storage boxes – great for stowing extra duvets and sheets.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>Ola Wihlborg</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/gladstad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NIEDEN</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/nieden/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/nieden/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=233</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The natural solid wood is beautiful as it is or you can make it more personal by staining, painting or waxing it. Also, the bed frame is high enough so you can place storage boxes underneath.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The compact design is perfect for tight spaces or under low ceilings, so you can make the most of your available space.<br />The hard-wearing solid pine has natural variations in grain, color and texture, giving every piece a unique look.<br />If you oil, wax, lacquer or stain the untreated solid wood surface it will be more durable and easy to care for.<br />There’s plenty of space under the bed for storage boxes &#8211; perfect for storing extra duvets and pillows.<br />You can easily vacuum under the bed frame to keep the space clean and dust-free.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/nieden/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BRIMNES</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/brimnes/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/brimnes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A bed frame with hidden storage in several places – perfect if you live in a small space. The BRIMNES series has several smart solutions that help you save space.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything is kept close at hand with integrated storage in the headboard.<br />Ample storage space is hidden neatly under the bed in 4 large drawers. Perfect for storing duvets, pillows and bed linen.<br />Hide cables for lamps and chargers by feeding them through the holes on the top of the headboard.<br />You can sit up comfortably in bed thanks to the high headboard; just prop some pillows behind your back and you will have a comfortable place to read or watch TV.<br />This versatile bed frame will look great with your choice of textiles and bedroom furniture.<br />Adjustable bed sides allow you to use mattresses of different thicknesses.<br />LURÖY slatted bed base with curved slats helps to absorb your body weight and supports your body, while the open construction allows air to circulate and keeps the mattress fresh.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>IKEA of Sweden/K Hagberg/M Hagberg</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/brimnes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MALM</title>
		<link>/index.php/product/malm/</link>
					<comments>/index.php/product/malm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bharat123]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product#038;p=231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A clean design with solid wood veneer. Place the bed on its own or with the headboard against a wall. If you need space for extra bedding, add MALM bed storage boxes on casters.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wood veneer gives you the same look, feel and beauty as solid wood with unique variations in grain, color and texture.<br />This versatile bed frame will look great with your choice of textiles and bedroom furniture.<br />You can sit up comfortably in bed thanks to the high headboard – just prop some pillows behind your back and you will have a comfortable place to read or watch TV.<br />You can easily vacuum under the bed frame to keep the space clean and dust-free.<br />Adjustable bed sides allow you to use mattresses of different thicknesses.<br />LURÖY slatted bed base with curved slats helps to absorb your body weight and supports your body, while the open construction allows air to circulate and keeps the mattress fresh.<br /><strong>Designer</strong>Eva Lilja Löwenhielm/IKEA of Sweden</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/index.php/product/malm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
